imagechef.com 2017-12-13

# ImageChef Privacy Policy

ImageChef Incorporated Privacy Information

Information Collection and Use

ImageChef collects aggregate statistical data on web site traffic.

ImageChef is a wholly owned subsidiary of CyberLink.com Corporation (U.S.), which together with CyberLink Europe B.V. (Netherlands), CyberLink Inc. (Japan) are the subsidiaries of CyberLink Corporation (Taiwan)(collectively CyberLink entities, or each individually CyberLink entity).

No user information or e-mail addresses is shared with any third parties other than CyberLink entity (entities), with the exception of what is required to release to our credit card gateway partner for executing a purchase. If any of the user information or e-mail address is shared with CyberLink entity (entities), it will be used to enhance the user experience of the provided service and to provide product/service information. CyberLink entity (entities) shall not sell such user information or e-mail address to any third parties for profits. To see CyberLink’s Privacy Statement, please visit <http://www.cyberlink.com/stat/company/enu/privacy-policy.jsp>.

ImageChef collects user submitted information such as name, email address, home or work address, phone number and age to authenticate users and also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, country, self-description, DVD region, preferred language, movie interests in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other and otherwise facilitate and enhance use of the ImageChef website ("Site") by its users. By using your Facebook login information to log into ImageChef, you also permit ImageChef to access your Facebook information, such as your profile information and privacy settings.

User profile information including members' pictures and user names are displayed on the Site in order to facilitate user interaction in the ImageChef social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join ImageChef, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the Site and its associated services. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on the Site with each other through the ImageChef services, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members.

Cookies

A cookie is a small text file containing information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use 'cookies' to monitor your visits to the Site, to analyze our site traffic patterns, and to provide a user-friendly registration and log-in process for your ease of use and to enhance our services and communication with you. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or to information beyond what you provide to us. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. Consult your browser's manual or online help if you want information on restricting or disabling the browser's handling of cookies. You may disable the collection of cookies in your browser settings. If you disable cookies, you can still view the publicly available information on our Site, but you will not be able to take advantage of offers or activities requiring a ImageChef All Access pass, which includes accessing user-only support areas. If you are using a shared computer and you have cookies turned on, be sure to log off when you finish accessing or using the Site.

Advertising Partners

CyberLink allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display and/or serve advertisements within the Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, or JavaScript) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

CyberLink does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have opted in. However, please note that if an advertiser asks CyberLink to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, men ages 28 - 40) or audience segment (for example, women in California who viewed certain content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you have the characteristics of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt out, once you have opted in, of certain practices. CyberLinks Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We implement Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"), to support Google features such as Display Advertising, Remarketing,Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online., Google uses cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Site, and also to report how our ad impressions, and uses of ad services are related to your visits to our Site. Google may show our ads on sites you use across the internet you use. You can also opt-out from being tracked by the aforegoing mentioned Google features for thein future by following the instructions shown in the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>

Some of our users may be shown a special offer after first registering on our site, offered by a partner. The user's personal information will be shown and he/she will be given the option of sending that information to the partner to sign up for a service, or to decline the offer.

Confidentiality and Security

For sales, credit card information is not stored by ImageChef. User passwords are stored in encrypted format so they may not be read by anyone. Our servers are stored in a secure remote facility.

Copyright © 2015 ImageChef Incorporated
